isumsoft.com 2018-01-09

# iSumsoft Privacy Policy

At iSumsoft, your security and privacy is the utmost importance to us. We will only collect your personal information for defined purposes. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you. We may share your information only with partners who adhere to iSumsoft's commitment to protect your privacy. iSumsoft will not sell your personal information in any manner whatsoever. As such, iSumsoft is committed to ensuring that its customers are informed as to how their personal information will be used and kept secure.

## Why we collect personal information?

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

## How we protect your personal information?

iSumsoft uses secure server hosted by 3rd party credit card processors that encrypt the entire customer's personal information including name, address, credit card number and credit card expiration date etc. before it is sent to us. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information. Your credit card information is only used for online transition.

## About Cookies

In order to better understand what services are valuable to our customers, we use "cookies". A cookie is a little text file composed of alphanumeric characters, which is created on your computer when your browser accesses a website that uses cookies. The files are used to help your browser navigate the website and fully use all its features like logins, preferences, language settings, themes, among other common features. The cookie is used solely to help your browser process a website, it doesn't collect any information from your computer or snoop on your files, and they cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. You can change the settings in your browser to prevent cookies if you do not want to have a cookie set when you visit our website. However, by doing so, you may not have full access to all the web pages.
